<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on April</title>
    <link>https://Zpn11.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on April</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:35:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://Zpn11.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Case Analysis: Gibbons v. Ogden (1824)</title>
      <link>https://Zpn11.github.io/projects/analyse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Zpn11.github.io/projects/analyse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Parties Involved:&#xA;Petitioner: Thomas Gibbons, a steamboat operator holding a federal license.&#xA;Respondent: Aaron Ogden, a steamboat operator with an exclusive state license granted by New York.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-background-of-the-dispute&#34;&gt;1. Background of the Dispute&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The conflict in Gibbons v. Ogden arose from overlapping state and federal authority over interstate commerce. In 1808, New York granted Robert Livingston and Robert Fulton an exclusive license to operate steamboats in the state&amp;rsquo;s waterways for 30 years. Aaron Ogden later purchased this franchise, allowing him to solely navigate New York waters. Concurrently, Thomas Gibbons obtained a federal license authorized by an act of Congress to operate steamboats between New York and New Jersey. Ogden sued Gibbons in a New York state court, arguing that the federal license infringed upon New York’s exclusive rights to its waterways. Gibbons contended that his operations constituted interstate commerce, thereby falling under federal jurisdiction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise interview </title>
      <link>https://Zpn11.github.io/projects/interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Zpn11.github.io/projects/interview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;company-profile&#34;&gt;Company Profile&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;SHENZHEN KINGDOM SCI-TECH, LTD Jiangmen Team(hereinafter referred to as &amp;ldquo;Jinzheng&amp;rdquo;).Jinzheng was founded in 1998 and listed on the Shanghai Stock Exchange in 2003. As of now, the registered capital is approximately 1 billion yuan. Jinzheng is China&amp;rsquo;s leading financial technology service provider, with branches in Shenzhen, Beijing and Shanghai, and two R&amp;amp;D centers in Chengdu and Nanjing. At present, the entire Jinzheng Group has more than 20 platforms and subsidiaries. The group employs more than 10,000 people.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The business direction of the Jiangmen team is the overall business of Jinzheng Group. Jinzheng has established a dual-circulation development strategy of &amp;ldquo;financial technology + digital economy&amp;rdquo; and completed the &amp;ldquo;four modernization framework&amp;rdquo; layout of digital industrialization, industrial digitization, digital governance, and data value in the field of digital economy. Jinzheng&amp;rsquo;s business covers traditional financial and inclusive financial fields such as securities, funds, banks, trusts, insurance, Internet finance, financial leasing, commercial factoring, quantitative investment, and third-party payment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Jinzheng is divided into five major business lines: the first is the securities field, the second is the fund field, the third is the banking field, the fourth is the Internet finance field, and the fifth is the smart city management field. The cornerstone of Jinzheng&amp;rsquo;s main business line is in the traditional financial field. The following mainly discusses the securities and fund fields. In the securities field, Jinzheng&amp;rsquo;s main products are to assist regulatory agencies such as the China Securities Regulatory Commission, the Securities Industry Association, the Fund Industry Association, and the China Securities Depository and Clearing Corporation to provide supervision and services. For example, Jinzheng provides China Lighting Company with a customized unified account platform for development; Jinzheng operates an over-the-counter trading system for the Hong Kong Stock Exchange. In the fund field, some of the counters of public funds holding gold certificates also have asset management systems. Including the Yu&amp;rsquo;ebao product launched by Jinzheng in 2013, the entire settlement is completed by Jinzheng; Jinzheng cooperates with Tianlong Fund to create a comprehensive trading system for its backend. The company has made progress in the fund industry, winning the bid for the Yimin Fund general contracting project and launching the next generation of digital transformation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;organizational-structure-and-organizational-management&#34;&gt;Organizational structure and Organizational management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organization of various departments of the company and coordination between departments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
